Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Information Center Records, 1890s-1987
J. Walter Thompson Company. Information Center records 1890s-1987
- Communications Committee Reports, 1956-1959, undated
  - Information folder:
    - No. 41, Report On Outdoor As An Advertising Medium, Media Research Department, 1958, Jan.
    - No. 42, 1956-57 Gross Advertising Revenue, Selected List of Magazines, Media Research Department, 1958, Feb.
    - No. 43, Circulation and Linage In Multiple Newspaper Markets, 1958, Apr.
    - No. 44, Evaluation Of An Advertising Campaign, 1958, Apr. 13
    - No. 45, Current Analysis of the Grocery Store Distributed Magazines, Media Research Department, 1958, Apr.
    - No. 46, The Changing Role Of The Advertising Agency, 1958, May
    - No. 47, A Creative Man's Gloom At The J. Walter Thompson Company Consumer Pand Personality Profile Studies, Research Department, 1958, July
    - No. 48, A Brief Resume Of The Drug Industry, 1958, Aug.
    - No. 49, Analysis Of Opportunities And Practices In the Premium Industry, Marketing and Merchandising Services, 1958, Spring
    - No. 50, Consumer Contests, Marketing and Merchandising Services, 1958, July
    - No. 51, The Creation And Production Of Animated Television Commercials With A Side Reference To The Emily Tipp Bread Series, undated
    - No. 52, Trend Of Volume Discounts In Daily Newspaper Rates, Media Research Department, 1958, Aug.
    - No. 53, Metro Area Television Home Ownership By State 1958, Media Research Department, 1958, July
    - No. 54, Principles of Television Network Audience Cumulation, 1958, July
    - No. 55, Regional Food Advertiser General Television Announcement Buying Strategy, Media Research Department, 1958, Sept.
    - No. S6, Analysis of Split-Run Facilities Available in Magazines and Supplements, Media Research Department, 1958, Sept.
    - No. 57, Summary of Neilsen Data on Television and Radio Audiences, Media Research Department, 1958, June
    - No. 58, An Analysis of Syndicated Film By Spot Television Announcements, 1958, Oct.
    - No. 59, J. Walter Thompson Company Looks At Video Tape And States Its Position, undated
    - No. 60, Magazine Advertising And the Housewife, Social Research, 1957, Oct.
    - No. 61, Television Terminology, 1956, Jan.
    - No. 62, The Portable Projector Television Commercial Testing System, Marketing Research Department, 1959, June
    - No. 63, Explanation of Broadcasting Ratings And Rating Services Available To J. Walter Thompson Company Media Research Section, 1959, Apr.
    - No. 64A, Report On Newspapers As An Advertising Medium, Media Research, 1959, March
    - No. 64B, Report On Magazines As An Advertising Medium, Media Research, 1959, March (Box 23)
    - No. 64C, Report On Radio As An Advertising Medium, Media Research, 1959, Apr.
    - No. 64D, Report On Television As An Advertising Medium, 1959, March
    - No. 64E, Report On Sunday Comics And Magazine Supplements As An Advertising Medium, Media Research, 1959, March
    - No. 64F, Report On Outdoor As An Advertising Medium, Media Research, 1959, March
    - No. 64G, Report On Theatre Advertising, Media Research, 1959, March
    - No. 65, Eastman Kodak Company Television Media Review, Media Research, undated
    - No. 66, Communicating With Retailas, Industrial and Professional Department, 1959, Feb.
    - No. 67, The J. Walter Thompson Company Consumer Panel, Market Research, undated
    - No. 68, Appraisal of Radio's Current Status And Guide To Its Future Use, Media and Programming Department, 1959, Jan.
    - No. 69, Radio Listening Habits And Attitudes Of The United States Housewife, Research Department, 1958, Nov.
    - No. 70, Advertising Budget Requirements 1958and 1959, Media Research Department, 1958, Oct.
    - No. 71, Putting Copy Research In Perspective, 1958, Sept.
    - No. 72, Evaluation of Network Television Circulation and Cost Trends, Media and Programming Departments, 1959, Feb.
    - No. 73, What 1,244 People Think Of Druggists, Prom American Druggist, 1958, Dec.
    - No. 74, An Analysis Of Printed Advertising Rating Methods, Research Department, 1958, Feb.
- Oversize Materials
  - Vertical Files Series
    - 1926-1981 (Folder 1)
    - Accounts, undated (Folder 2)
    - Accounts: Prizes and Contests, Fleishshmann's, 1923-1924 (Folder 3)
    - Accounts: Lever Brothers, 1940-1982 (Box OV1)
    - Accounts: Volunteer, 1967-1971
    - History, 1959-1983
    - History: Awards, 1984 (Folder 4)
    - Organization, 1954-1983 (Box OV1)
      - Domestic: New York Office, 1950-1957?
      - Domestic: New York Office, Training, 1964-1967
      - International, 1957-1983
    - Organization: International, India, undated (Folder 5)
    - Organization: International, United Kingdom, undated
    - Organization: International, United Kingdom, 1953-1985 (Box OV1)
  - Communications Committee Reports Series
    - Communications Committee Reports: (Box OV1)
      - Information Folder, 1958
      - No. 2, Copy Reports at Low Cost, undated (Folder 6)
        [Packaging and Labels for Dietz Bread/Hathaway Bakeries; advertisements for J. Walter Thompson, Indiana Bell, American Red Cross and others]
      - No. 21, J. Walter Thompson--Company Structure, undated (Box OV1)
      - No. 36, The Effectiveness of Industrial Advertising, 1957, Nov.